<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jing Zhang</title><link>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Jing Zhang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="http://www.jingzhang.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/about/</guid><description>I am currently a Master student concentrating in Data Analytics along with a Bachelor of Science degree in Operational Research and Information Engineering from Cornell University. My professional interests lies with the areas of data analytics, programming, and optimization. Lastly, I hope to obtain an full time analyst opportunity in order to enhance my experience in the financial, analytical, and software fields. I am proficient in languages and technologies such as: Python (Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-learn, SciPy, Matplotlib), SQL, RStudio, Looker, Tableau, Microsoft Excel (Pivot Tables, VLOOKUP, VBA), Java, HTML/CSS, and Amplide.</description></item><item><title>Contact Me</title><link>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/contact/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s Get In Touch! Feel free to reach out at anytime for feedbacks, comments, or coffee chats. I can be reached by email, text, and phone calls.
✉️ : wz223@cornell.edu
📞 : (917)-526-0185</description></item><item><title>Interests</title><link>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/interests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/interests/</guid><description>Sports 🏀 Travel ✈️ Music 🎵 Food 🍚 I am been playing basketball for 9 years, including high school variety and college intramural. In particular, I love the sport because its team oriented and allows me to only focus on the game itself. One of my favorite hobby is traveling. I have been to China, Japan, Paris, Rome, Korea and a bunch of other places.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.jingzhang.example.com/projects/</guid><description>Braze Inc. Unchecked Inbound Accounts: Performed data imputing and examined through trends within unidentified inbound accounts with the Sales Operations team
Mobile Adoption Rate: Investigated mobile messaging products in order to improve user’s rate of adoption with the Product Marketing team
Aabix Corp. Mold Growth Algorithm: Implemented fault detection algorithms on real-time data to eliminated and predicted mold growth across a certain period of time using Pandas and NumPy</description></item></channel></rss>